

Hanifa Nurfajari

Bekasi, Jawa Barat, 17510 | +62 838 9863 2854 | <u>Hanifanurfajari26@gmail.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/hanifa-nurfajari/</u>

PROFILE

Hi! I'm an enthusiast person who has interest in Social Media and Digital Marketing. Have various experiences in creating content and handling Social Media. I'm good at copywriting and able to analyze social media insight. I always passionate to expand my knowledge and experience by keep learning.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

TOOLS

- Social Media Platform
- Facebook Ads Manager
- Google Ads Manager
- Social Blade
- Social Bakers
- Google Analytics
- Canva
- VN (Video Editor)

SPECIALITIES

- Initiative
- Creative Thinking
- Critical Thinking
- Detail Oriented

WORK EXPERIENCES

PT Multi Indocitra (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Digital Marketing Intern (July 2019 – January 2020)

- Create content plan on social media Facebook, Instagram, YouTube
- Posting content and handling brand on all social media channels
- Manage endorsement and KOL (Key Opinion Leader)
- Advertising on social media platform
- Analyze other beauty and personal care brands

ANDAF CORPORATION (Bekasi, Indonesia)

Content Writer/Copywriter (June - December 2020)

- Create content plan for several Brand on social media
- Create brief design content on the several Brand social media

KIBIF GROUP (Jakarta, Indonesia)

Social Media Officer (May 2021 – April 2022)

- Create content plan on social media Instagram, Facebook, Tiktok
- Handling brand on social media
- Create a social media strategy
- Handling website of KIBIF

- KOL (Key Opinion Leader) Management
- Advertising on Instagram & Facebook

EDUCATION

FORMAL

PPM School of Manajemen (2016-2020)

Bachelor degree of Business Management - GPA 3,71

NON FORMAL

RAKAMIN ACADEMY (Feb – Jun 2022)

Bootcamp Digital Marketing

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Student Executive Board PPM School of Management (2018-2019)

Staff Division of Social Community

REFERENCE

Intan Ginasti
Digital Marketing at Sentral Sistem Consulting
lntan.ginasti@gmail.com
085711589435